(Let it go.)
=Revenge From A Wife=
=Episode 8=
(Physician)
Help me!
Miss!
What happened?
I was bitten while I was out.
Miss, you've been poisoned
by snake venom.
I need to drain
the tainted blood right away.
This may hurt.
Try to bear with it.
Take these medicines as directed.
All right.
Thank you, Ms. Xiaoqing.
Can you stand?
I've drained the tainted blood.
If you'd come an hour later,
you would've lost this arm.
Thank you, miss.
Mr. Gu.
Get the pain-relief powder.
All right.
Here.
Thank you.
Your Maj...
Thank you, sir.
Avoid meat and fish for a few days.
Change the dressing once a day.
All right.
I'll send someone by later
with the fee.
I'll take my leave.
We're out of firewood.
I'll go get some.
All right.
Please spare my life!
I swear I won't tell anyone
who you really are.
Don't kill me!
I like that I'm just Mr. Gu to her.
No one gets to ruin that.
Take her back
to Minister Liu's residence.
Tell Minister Liu
his daughter was killed
by bandits on her way home.
I'll have the Capital Prefecture
investigate thoroughly.
Yes.
Done.
Hold this.
See?
This part...
goes around the back.
Didn't you do that yourself?
♪Peach blossoms fill your window again♪
There. I've got it now.
You've got it?
You're hopeless.
Why can't you get it?
It looks good to me.
And you're laughing?
Look at what you made.
What's this?
What even is this?
Still laughing at me?
Run! Run!
You still dare laugh at me?
♪A quiet sigh♪
♪Longing hides hope between the lines♪
♪A ray of spring brings warmth♪
♪A tree bursts into bloom♪
♪Across hills and rivers, I await you♪
♪Borrow half a city's warmth♪
♪For half a lifetime of love♪
♪May we have a lifetime of peace♪
♪I only wish you'd stay with me forever♪
♪A ray of spring brings warmth♪
♪A tree bursts into bloom♪
♪Across hills and rivers, I await you♪
♪Sharing the warmth of spring♪
♪May half a lifetime's wish come true♪
♪Borrow a whole city's warmth♪
♪I only wish your heart were like mine♪
♪Side by side♪
I heard Guizhen Cottage
was built by His Majesty
for the late Empress.
What do you think
of the cottage?
It may look simple,
but I hear more went into it
than even a palace.
Yet so many people go hungry.
Why build on such a grand scale
for someone who's already gone?
That's what I thought at first.
But later,
I heard the elders nearby
often tell stories about
His Majesty and the late Empress,
and I changed my mind.
This isn't extravagance.
It's devotion.
So much in this world
fades away.
Reputation.
Glory.
Even true feelings can fade.
To find someone
who cares for you that sincerely
is truly rare.
♪If I could be with you♪
(Sometimes I've thought that)
(if I ever met someone)
(who truly cared for me,)
(I'd gladly marry him)
(and spend my life by his side,)
(and grow old together.)
♪Through a thousand twists and turns♪
♪I would stay only for you♪
♪Sunset fades beyond the lonely city♪
♪Dusk snow paints the green hills♪
♪A lone rider storms the old pass♪
♪Drunk, I gaze by lamplight♪
♪Old friends have all drifted away♪
♪My broken sword rusts, as do I♪
♪Jackdaws cry into the night♪
♪Half a banner snaps in the wind♪
♪In dreams, I return to the camps♪
♪Moonlight chills my armor♪
♪Life is a dream through many winters♪
♪I gaze beyond the edge of the world♪
♪Parting sorrow spills across the moon♪
♪The moon and wind mean nothing now♪
♪History turns to ash before ink dries♪
♪Who plays the zither
and sighs at the pavilion?♪
♪The past has faded away♪